var questions =[
    {
        heading:'PASSAGE ONE',
        content:'Checked shirts are now synonymous with the technology entrepreneur. Whilst nobody can be attributed with starting the craze, technology whiz-kids from Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg to Twitter co-founder Eva William are sporting these criss-crossed personal statements. This open-necked checked shirt look is beginning to be emulated by American teenagers. The important question being asked by fashion retailers is whether this trend will grow beyond it’s currently niche audience to the mass market. Fashion trends are fickle and if retailers get it wrong they are quickly punished through falling revenue. That is why fashion outlet Dicies often attend social gatherings and exhibitions where they expect to find lots of young people; their thinking is that if they can observe fashion trends and be ahead of the curve they will get a larger slice of the fashion pie.',
        question:'Twitter was founded by more than one person.',
        optionA:'false',
        optionB:'True',
        optionC:'neither',
        optionD:'either',
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        heading:'PASSAGE ONE',
        content:'Checked shirts are now synonymous with the technology entrepreneur. Whilst nobody can be attributed with starting the craze, technology whiz-kids from Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg to Twitter co-founder Eva William are sporting these criss-crossed personal statements. This open-necked checked shirt look is beginning to be emulated by American teenagers. The important question being asked by fashion retailers is whether this trend will grow beyond it’s currently niche audience to the mass market. Fashion trends are fickle and if retailers get it wrong they are quickly punished through falling revenue. That is why fashion outlet Dicies often attend social gatherings and exhibitions where they expect to find lots of young people; their thinking is that if they can observe fashion trends and be ahead of the curve they will get a larger slice of the fashion pie.',
        question:'Mark Zuckerberg started the trend for wearing checked shirts.',
        optionA:'neither',
        optionB:'false',
        optionC:'True',
        optionD:'either',
        answer: '2'

    },
    {
        heading:'PASSAGE TWO',
        content:'Scientist now claim that some of the low, wide debris-covered formations first observed on radar images of mars as far back as the 1970s are in fact glaciers around 1km thick.some scientist believe that mars contains ice outside the polar caps which have been a matter of discussion. It is believe that radar technology did not exist before 1980.',
        question:'Some scientist believe that Mars contains ice outside the polar caps.',
        optionA:'false',
        optionB:'true',
        optionC:'neither',
        optionD:'either',
        answer: '2'   
    },
    {
        heading:'PASSAGE TWO',
        content:'Scientist now claim that some of the low, wide debris-covered formations first observed on radar images of mars as far back as the 1970s are in fact glaciers around 1km thick.some scientist believe that mars contains ice outside the polar caps which have been a matter of discussion. It is believe that radar technology did not exist before 1980.',
        question:'Radar technology existed before to the 1980s ',
        optionA:'neither',
        optionB:'true',
        optionC:'false',
        optionD:'either',
        answer: '3'   
    },
    {   heading:'',
        content:'VERBAL SECTION',
        question:'Choose the opposite of Good',
        optionA:'bad',
        optionB:'fine',
        optionC:'nice',
        optionD:'worst',
        answer:'1'
    },
    {   heading:'',
        content:'VERBAL SECTION',
        question:'Choose the opposite of peace',
        optionA:'live',
        optionB:'war',
        optionC:'life',
        optionD:'piece',
        answer:'2'
    },
    {   heading:'',
        content:'Quatitative',
        question:'What is the sum of 2 + 4 =',
        optionA:'8',
        optionB:'7',
        optionC:'6',
        optionD:'5',
        answer:'3'   
    },
    {   heading:'',
        content:'Quatitative',
        question:'What is the Area of a square with side 2',
        optionA:'6',
        optionB:'8',
        optionC:'4',
        optionD:'2',
        answer:'3'   
    },
    {   heading:'',
    content:'Quatitative',
    question:'What is the perimeter of a rectangle of width 3 and length 6',
    optionA:'6',
    optionB:'10',
    optionC:'36',
    optionD:'18',
    answer:'4'   
},
{   heading:'',
content:'Quatitative',
question:'What is the square of 5',
optionA:'50',
optionB:'10',
optionC:'25',
optionD:'125',
answer:'3'   
}
];
























































